freesaver.com 2010-05-16

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy policy**

Freesaver.Com is deeply committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users.  
We do not collect or save any personal information about our visitors and will not send any unsolicited information (spam) to anyone.   

We log statistical information about browsers, operating systems, and referring websites for security purposes, and to further improve this website. None of this information is distributed to any third party.  

Freesaver.Com works with third parties that serve ads to this site. These ads may contain cookies but we do not have access to this information. To find out more about how these sponsors manage the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please visit their privacy pages for additional information: 

Companies advertising through Burst Media network may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.burstmedia.com/consumer_optout.asp). 

Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network [privacy policy](http://www.google.co.uk/privacy_ads.html).

Click for [Freeze Privacy Policy](http://www.freeze.com/Policies/Privacy.aspx)

* * * * * 

Freesaver.com site contains links to other sites. We do not accept any responsibility for the privacy practices or content of these Web sites. These links are provided in good faith, and we cannot be held responsible for any subsequent changes in character or content of the sites we are linking to.
